<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN"
                    "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd">

<book>
  <title>&productname; User Manual</title>

  <author>Indigo Riceway</author>

  <preface id="preface">  
    <title>Preface</title>

    <sect1 id="about">
      <title>Availability</title>

<!-- Note to author: maybe put a picture here? -->

      <para>

The information in this manual is available in the following forms:
      </para>

      <itemizedlist>

        <listitem><para>
Instant telepathic injection
        </para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>
Lumino-goggle display
        </para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>
Ink on compressed, dead, arboreal matter
        </para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>
Cuneiform etched in clay tablets
        </para></listitem>
      </itemizedlist>

      <para>
The &productname; is sold in galactic pamphlet boutiques or wherever 
&companyname; equipment can be purchased. For more information, or 
to order a copy by hyperspacial courier, please visit our universe-wide 
Web page at <systemitem 

role="url">http://www.cybertronix.com/sonic_screwdrivers.html</systemitem>.
      </para>
    </sect1>

    <sect1 id="disclaimer">
      <title>Notice</title>
      <para>
While <emphasis>every</emphasis>

effort has been taken to ensure the accuracy and
usefulness of this guide, we cannot be held responsible for the
occasional inaccuracy or typographical error.
      </para>
    </sect1>
  </preface>


  <chapter id="intro">

    <title>Introduction</title>

    <para>
Congratulations on your purchase of one of the most valuable tools in
the universe! The &companyname; &productname; is
equipment no hyperspace traveller should be without. Some of the
myriad tasks you can achieve with this device are:
    </para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem><para>
Pick locks in seconds. Never be locked out of your tardis
again. Good for all makes and models including Yale, Dalek, and
Xngfzz.
      </para></listitem>
      <listitem><para>
Spot-weld metal, alloys, plastic, skin lesions, and virtually any
other material.
      </para></listitem>
      <listitem><para>
Rid your dwelling of vermin. Banish insects, rodents, and computer
viruses from your time machine or spaceship.
      </para></listitem>
      <listitem><para>
Slice and process foodstuffs from tomatoes to brine-worms. Unlike a
knife, there is no blade to go dull.
      </para></listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
    <para>
Here is what satisfied customers are saying about their &companyname;
&productname;:
    </para>

    <comment> 

Should we name the people who spoke these quotes?  --Ed.
    </comment>

    <blockquote>
      <para>
<quote>It helped me escape from the prison planet Garboplactor VI. I
wouldn't be alive today if it weren't for my Cybertronix 9000.</quote>
      </para>
    </blockquote>

    <blockquote>
      <para>
<quote>As a bartender, I have to mix martinis <emphasis>just
right</emphasis>. Some of my customers get pretty cranky if I slip
up. Luckily, my new sonic screwdriver from Cybertronix is so accurate,
it gets the mixture right every time. No more looking down the barrel
of a kill-o-zap gun for this bartender!</quote>
      </para>
    </blockquote>


  </chapter>

  <chapter id="controls">
    <title>Mastering the Controls</title>

    <sect1>
      <title>Overview</title>

      <para>
<xref linkend="controls-diagram"/> is a diagram of the parts of your
&productname;.
      </para>

      <figure id="controls-diagram">

        <title>Exploded Parts Diagram</title>
        <graphic fileref="parts.gif"/>
      </figure>

      <para>
<xref linkend="controls-table"/>

lists the function of the parts labeled in the diagram.
      </para>

      <table id="controls-table">

        <title>Control Descriptions</title>
        <tgroup cols="2">
          <thead>
            <row>
              <entry>Control</entry>
              <entry>Purpose</entry>
            </row>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <row>
              <entry>Decoy Power Switch</entry>
              <entry><para>
Looks just like an on-off toggle button, but only turns on a small
flashlight when pressed. Very handy when your &productname; is misplaced
and discovered by primitive aliens who might otherwise accidentally
injure themselves.
              </para></entry>
            </row>
            <row>
              <entry><emphasis>Real</emphasis> Power Switch</entry>
              <entry><para>
An invisible fingerprint-scanning capacitance-sensitive on/off switch.
              </para></entry>
            </row>
            ...
            <row>
              <entry>The <quote>Z</quote> Twiddle Switch</entry>
              <entry><para>
We're not entirely sure what this does. Our lab testers have had
various results from teleportation to spontaneous
liquification. <emphasis role="bold">Use at your own risk!</emphasis>
              </para></entry>
            </row>
          </tbody>
        </tgroup>
      </table>

      <note>
        <para>
A note to arthropods: Stop forcing your inflexible appendages to adopt
un-ergonomic positions. Our new claw-friendly control template is
available. 
        </para>
      </note>

      <sect2 id="power-sect">
        <title>Power Switch</title>

        <sect3 id="decoy-power-sect">
          <title>Why a decoy?</title>

          <comment>
Talk about the Earth's Tunguska Blast of 1908 here.
          </comment>
        </sect3>
      </sect2>
    </sect1>

    <sect1>
      <title>The View Screen</title>
      <para>
The view screen displays error messages and warnings, such as a
<errorcode>LOW-BATT</errorcode>

(low battery) message.<footnote> 

        <para>
The advanced model now uses a direct psychic link to the user's
visual cortex, but it should appear approximately the same as the more
primitive liquid crystal display.
        </para>

</footnote> When your &productname; starts up, it should
show a status display like this: 
      </para>

                  

      <screen>STATUS DISPLAY
BATT: 1.782E8 V
TEMP: 284 K
FREQ: 9.32E3 Hz
WARRANTY: ACTIVE</screen>
    </sect1>

    <sect1>
      <title>The Battery</title>
      <para>
Your &productname; is capable of generating tremendous amounts of
energy. For that reason, any old battery won't do. The power source is
a tiny nuclear reactor containing a piece of ultra-condensed plutonium
that provides up to 10 megawatts of power to your device. With a
half-life of over 20 years, it will be a long time before a
replacement is necessary.
      </para>
    </sect1>
  </chapter>
</book>